PRITEE PATEL

Ahmedabad, Gujarat Mo .No:9265917638

Mail ID:ppritee20@gmail.com

To be an efficient performer in all the aspect of my work by optimally utilizing my skills and potentials and fulfilling in the field of Banking and finance that would use my knowledge and experience which would help in the growth of organization.

Work Experience

Credit Processing Associate

03/2022 - Present

Centrum Housing Finance Limited

Ahmedabad

- Initial Review of the document received as per the Document Checklist.
- Entry in the System for logging case.
- Basic entry of financial reports in the cam format.
- Banking Analysis.
- Financial Analysis.

Sales Coordinator 01/2021 - 03/2022

Yes Bank

Ahmedabad

- Coordinating the sales team by managing schedules, filing important documents and communicating relevant information
- Ensuring the adequacy of sales-related equipment or material
- Handle the processing of all Files with accuracy and timeliness
- Inform clients of unforeseen delays or problems

Sales Coordinator 03/2019 - 05/2020

Bajaj Housing Finance Limited

Ahmedabad

- Worked alongside sales representatives to boost sales by enhancing product presentations and advertising collateral.
- Visited customer locations to evaluate requirements, demonstrate product offerings and propose strategic solutions for diverse needs.
- Managed efficient RFP database and responses, generating timely reports to inform Sales Manager.
- Developed new accounts by marketing company product and offering value-added services.

Assistant Import Executive

08/2018 - 02/2019

Bhagvati Colour PVT. LTD.

Ahmedabad

- Checking import and export documentation to determine cargo contents and classified goods into different
- tariff or fee groups.
- Created spreadsheets using Microsoft Excel for daily, weekly and monthly reporting.
- · Quickly learned new skills and applied them to daily tasks, improving efficiency and productivity.
- Worked with Export Manager to maintain optimum level of communication to effectively and efficiently
- complete projects.

Back Office Executive 08/2017 - 07/2018

Mahadev Enterprise

Ahmedabad

- Maintained daily updated calendars to assist management team in scheduling associates and external
- customers for meetings
- Maintained inventory for back-office supplies, computers and work-stations.
- Received purchase orders and processed invoices for payment.

- · Supervised processing of orders, order tracking and delivery of goods
- Prepared schedule for back-office tasks and employees' daily functions.

Education

Bachelor Of Commerce 03/2014 - 03/2017

Gujarat University Ahmedabad, Gujarat

High school or equivalent H.S.C. 03/2012 - 03/2014

Saraswati Vidhya Mandir Ahmedabad, Gujarat

Senior Secondary Certificate 03/2012

Saraswati Vidhya Mandir Ahmedabad, Gujarat

Languages Known

English, Hindi, and Gujarati

Skills

MS Office, Excel and PowerPoint

Excellent technical background and accurate analysis, Good documentation with computer knowledge. Analytical skills

Declaration

I hereby declared that all the information furnished above is true to the best of my knowledge.

Place: Ahmedabad

Pritee Patel